Finding Aid for the The James D. Squires Papers
Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I: Journalism career (1972-1989)
  - Horse of a Different Color
    - Box 44: Notes, correspondence, miscellaneous, clippings
      - Incoming correspondence - Abramson, Rudy-Korda, Michael (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kotas, John (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Lampton, Nana-Oxley, Jack (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Patterson, David (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence - Petter, Stanley D.-Young, William T. Jr. (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence - unidentified (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Outgoing correspondence, May 13, 2001-June 19, 2001; n.d. (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Publicity slick (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Pictures printed from www.horsephotos.com (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Clippings - Horse of a Different Color review (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Clippings - Seabiscuit review (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Box 45: Clippings and publications - Horses and people Clippings and publications - Horses
      - Monarchos, March 12, 2001-January 28, 2002; n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Point Given, May 5, 2001-August 27, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Point Given, The Blood-Horse March 24, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Point Given, The Blood-Horse June 16, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Point Given, Daily Racing Form April 29, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Point Given, The Saratogian “Pink Sheet,” August 25, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Point Given, The Saratogian August 26, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Regal Band - n.d. Clippings and publications - People (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Abdullah, Khalid (Juddmonte Farms), Keeneland Summer 2001 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Baffert, Bob, June 9, 1997-June 23, 2001; n.d. (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - bin Salman, Prince Ahmed (Thoroughbred Corp., owner Point Given), May 2, 2001-June 12, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Chavez, Jorge, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Hancock, Arthur B. III, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Hofmeister, George, 1998-June 21, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Magnier, John (Coolmore), August 18, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - al Maktoum, Sheiks Maktoum and Mohammed bin Rashid (Godolphin Racing), April 19, 1999-April 22, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Oxley, Debby and John (owners Monarchos), June 26, 2001; n.d. (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Sekiguchi, Fusao (owner Fusaichi Pegasus), 2000 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Squires, James D., April 29, 2001-May 21, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Squires, James D., Daily Racing Form May 13, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Squires, James D., New Yorker May 7, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Squires, James D., Orlando Magazine October 2001 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Stronach, Frank, January 29, 2001-August 18, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Ward, Donna and John, May 3, 2001-July 26, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Wooten, Gordon and Mary Lou (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Multiple people, April 16, 2001-July 28, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Multiple people, Thoroughbred Times June 30, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Fragments (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Box 46: Clippings and publications - Races (Florida Derby, Wood Memorial, Kentucky Derby)
      - Florida Derby, February 20, 2001-March 13, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Florida Derby - Fragments (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Florida Derby, The Blood-Horse March 17, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Florida Derby, Thoroughbred Times March 17, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Wood Memorial, April 14, 2001-April 15, 2001; n.d. (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Kentucky Derby, March 10, 2001-April 14, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Kentucky Derby, April 16, 2001-May 5, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Kentucky Derby, May 6, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Kentucky Derby, May 7, 2001-June 12, 2001; n.d. (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Kentucky Derby - Fragments (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Kentucky Derby - Fragments (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Kentucky Derby, The Blood-Horse, April 28, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Kentucky Derby, The Blood-Horse, May 12, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Box 47: Clippings and publications - Races (Kentucky Derby, Preakness Stakes)
      - Kentucky Derby, Daily Racing Form, May 5, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Kentucky Derby, Lexington Herald-Leader May 7, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Kentucky Derby, Louisville Courier-Journal May 6, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Kentucky Derby, State Journal-Register (Springfield, Ill.) Sports section, May 6, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Kentucky Derby, Thoroughbred Times, May 12, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Preakness Stakes, May 7, 2001-May 20, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Preakness Stakes, Fragments (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Preakness Stakes, Baltimore Sun Section D, May 19, 2001-May 20, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Box 48: Clippings and publications - Races (Belmont Stakes), sales, miscellaneous Race programs -Kentucky Derby Clippings and publications Races
      - Belmont Stakes, May 20, 2001-June 9, 2001; n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Belmont Stakes, Daily Racing Form, June 9, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Belmont Stakes, Thoroughbred Times, June 16, 2001 Sales (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - January 21, 1995-July 25, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - September 29, 2000-June 9, 2001; n.d. (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Keeneland Spring 2001 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Keeneland sale magazine, Spring 2001 Journal by Andy Plattner, appeared serially in The Backstretch magazine (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - March 2001 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - April 2001 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - May 2001 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - June 2001 Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - October 21, 1995-November 23, 2003; n.d. (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Fragments (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Lexington Herald-Leader Sports section, July 13, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - The Saratogian August 27, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Thoroughbred Times, June 24, 1995 Race programs (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Kentucky Derby programs (2) (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Box 49: Race programs (Preakness Stakes, Belmont Stakes), statistics, sale data, miscellaneous, original faxes and clippings Race programs
      - Preakness Stakes program (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Preakness Stakes souvenir magazine (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Belmont Stakes program (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Belmont Stakes post parade magazine Statistics (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Fast charts (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Past performance reports (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Workout times (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Race sheet - Gulfstream Park allowance race, February 3, 2001 Sales (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Misc. sale data (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Fasig-Tipton Saratoga Selected Yearlings August 2001 sale book Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Horse quotes (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Aga Khan history (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Photocopy of The Look of Eagles, by John Taintor Foote (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Lexington, Ken. weather data, January 1995 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous Originals (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Incoming correspondence - Bluewater Sales, LLC-Stephens, Nancy (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Clippings, March 2001 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Clippings, April 2001 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Clippings, May 2, 2001-May 5, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Clippings, May 6, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Clippings, May 7, 2001-May 14, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Clippings, May 17, 2001-May 20, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Clippings, June 19, 2001-November 23, 2003; n.d. (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Series IV: University courses (1990-1992)
    - Box 50: Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government material
      - Incoming correspondence - Dunn, Nancy-Trainor, Mick; unidentified (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Outgoing correspondence, May 9, 1990-July 23, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Phone message (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Syllabi for S-412: Business, Technology, and the Free Press (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Kennedy School information, faculty lists, course lists (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Lecture notes - Television’s impact on the democratic process (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Lecture notes - Research on television images (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Lecture notes - First Amendment Series: Pentagon Papers (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Lecture notes - The impact of television on news media (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Lecture notes - General changes in mass communication (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Lecture notes - The essence of communication (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Lecture notes - untitled (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Cronkite, Walter. Theodore H. White Lecture. Joan Shorenstein Barone Center on the Press, Politics and Public Policy, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University. November 15, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Discussion paper - Buhl, Dieter. “Window to the West: How Television from the Federal Republic Influenced Events in East Germany” (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Discussion paper - Duncan, Dayton. “Press, Polls, and the 1988 Campaign: An Insider’s Critique” (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Discussion paper - Grossman, Lawrence K. “Reflections on Television’s Role in American Presidential Elections” (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Discussion paper - Jakobson, Linda. “Lies in Ink, Truth in Blood: The Role and Impact of the Chinese Media During the Beijing Spring of ‘89” (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Research paper - Adatto, Kiku. “Sound Bite Democracy: Network Evening News Presidential Campaign Coverage, 1968 and 1988” (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Research paper - Lanouette, William. “Tritium and the Times: How the Nuclear Weapons-Production Scandal Became a National Story” (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Box 51: Middle Tennessee State University course material, course readings for Harvard and MTSU
      - Incoming correspondence - Badger, David-Wyatt, Robert; unidentified (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Journalism 430: Reviewing and Criticism (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Journalism 480: Seminar in Current Mass Media Issues - The Press and Democracy (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Student papers (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Attendance sheets (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Lecture notes (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Lecture notes (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Sample reviews and handouts (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Sample reviews and handouts (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Clippings - March 29, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Clippings - October 9, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Clippings, April 1992 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Course readings - untitled questionnaire (political update) (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Course readings - Anderson, John. “Brave New Inquirer.” Philadelphia, July 1991, 78-94 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Course readings - Branch, Taylor. “Outsiders and Insiders: Race and American History.” John S. Knight lecture, Stanford University, Stanford, CA, February 13, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Course readings - Batten, James K. “Profit and Quality.” Washington Journalism Review (July/August 1990): 31-34 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Course readings - Eason, David. “On Journalistic Authority: The Janet Cooke Scandal.” Critical Studies in Mass Communication 3 (1986): 429-447 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Course readings - Friendly, Fred. “The Birth of Another Rag.” In Minnesota Rag, New York: Vintage Books, 1982 Friendly, Fred. “Gagging ‘A Malicious, Scandalous and Defamatory Newspaper.’” In Minnesota Rag, New York: Vintage Books, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Course readings - Gannett Foundation. “Covering the Literacy Story: A Primer for Journalists on a Major Social Issue.” Conference report. Arlington, VA: Gannett Foundation, July 22, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Course readings - Ghiglione, Loren. “Introduction.” In The Buying and Selling of America’s Newspapers, edited by Loren Ghiglione. Indianapolis, IN: R.J. Berg, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - Course readings - Gray, Lloyd and Tony Tharp. “Delta Democrat-Times.” In The Buying and Selling of America’s Newspapers, edited by Loren Ghiglione. Indianapolis, IN: R.J. Berg, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Course readings - Griffith, Thomas. “Press Lords and Media Barons.” n.p.: n.d., 1-10 (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Course readings - Halberstam, David. The Powers that Be. New York: Knopf, 1979. 790-817 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Course readings - Hartman, Lynn Wickham. “Standards Governing the News: Their Use, Their Character, and Their Legal Implications. Iowa Law Review 72 (3) (March 1987). 637-700. (reprinted) (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Box 52: Course readings, MTSU and Harvard; publications; original clippings.
      - Course readings - “Hustler Magazine and Larry C. Flynt, Petitioners v. Jerry Falwell.” Supreme Court Reporter 108 (1988), 876-882 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Course readings - “Keepers of the Dollars.” 183-203 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Course readings - Kreig, Andrew. “Market Failures in Media Antitrust Regulation.” Paper submitted for independent study with Cass Sunstein, University of Chicago Law School, Chicago, IL, January 15, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Course readings - Kwitny, Jonathan. “The High Cost of High Profits.” Washington Journalism Review (June 1990): 19-34 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Course readings - Leapman, Michael. “Sock, Sock, Sock, Day After Day.” In Barefaced Cheek: The Apotheosis of Rupert Murdoch. London: Hodder and Stoughton, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Course readings - Lundberg, Kirsten. “General Electric and the National Broadcasting Co.: A Clash of Cultures.” Paper prepared for Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Course readings - McClatchy, C.K. “How Newspapers are Owned—And Does it Matter?” Press-Enterprise Lecture Series 23, January 27, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Course readings - Milburn, Michael and Anne McGrail. “The Dramatic Presentation of News and its Effects on Cognitive Complexity.” Paper presented at annual meeting of the International Society of Political Psychology, Washington, D.C., June 12, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Course readings - Nightingale, Suzan. “Anchorage Daily News.” In The Buying and Selling of America’s Newspapers, edited by Loren Ghiglione (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Course readings - Rowland, Willard D. Jr. “The Case of the United States: A History and Analysis of Public-Service Broadcasting in the U.S.—Its Mandate, Institutions and Conflicts.” Paper contribution to Public-Service Broadcasting in a Multichannel Environment, a project of the Washington Program of the Annenberg Schools of Communications, October 1990 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Course readings - Schwartz, John, Carolyn Friday, Peter McKillop and Karen Springen. “Time: The Counterattack.” Newsweek, June 26, 1989. 48-53 Griffith, Thomas. “What’s so Special About News Magazines?” Newsweek, June 26, 1989. 52-53 Hammer, Joshua. “The Myth of Global Synergy.” Newsweek, June 26, 1989. 54 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Course readings - “The State of the Italian Media: Newsmakers Become Newsowners—A Case Study of La Republica” (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Course readings - Weaver, David H. “Setting Political Priorities: What Role for the Press?” Roy W. Howard Public Lecture in Journalism and Mass Communication Research, Indiana University-Bloomington, Bloomington, IN, April 16, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Course readings - Whited, Charles. “A World Divided.” In Knight: A Publisher in the Tumultuous Century by Charles Whited. New York: Dutton, 1988. Whited, Charles. “The Days of Lightning.” In Knight: A Publisher in the Tumultuous Century by Charles Whited. New York: Dutton, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Course readings - Whited, Charles. “An Age of Excesses.” In Knight: A Publisher in the Tumultuous Century by Charles Whited. New York: Dutton, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Course readings - miscellaneous fragments (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Publications - 1990 Ownership Survey April 1990 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Publications - The Bulletin November 1990 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Publications - Collins, Keith S., ed. Responsibility and Freedom in the Press: Are they in Conflict? n.p.: Citizen’s Choice, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Publications - Presstime, June 1990 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Original clippings (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Series V: Biographical material, miscellaneous correspondence, writings
    - Box 53: Material covering dates, [1955]-1972; 1990-2004
      - Resumes and curriculum vitae (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - “First story ever”—8th or 9th grade [1955] (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous material from U.S. Army service (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Beasley, John S. II-Huddleston, Stephen (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kelly, Timothy (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kinser, Todd-Snyder, Rob (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Outgoing correspondence, April 11, 1994-September 23, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Byline file, October 8, 1990-March 26, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Byline file, April 2, 2000-July 30, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Byline file, August 2, 2000-September 24, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Byline file, October 5, 2000-December 3, 2000; n.d. (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, March 11, 1993-September 2000 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Publications - Columbia Journalism Review, March/April 2001 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Speeches (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Original clippings - 1990-2000; n.d. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Series VI: Multimedia
    - Videocassettes - Beta and VHS formats
      - VHS - Sales conference, September 14-September 15, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - VHS - James Squires on “Chicago Tonight” with John Callaway, WTTW-TV Chicago, January 9, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - VHS - “Ovie’s Millstone” Chicago Tribune, March 17, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - VHS - James Squires on “Your Government” with Sue Wiley, April 1991 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - VHS - James Squires on “Comment on Kentucky” for Read All About It!, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - VHS - C-SPAN viewer call-in program for Read All About It!, February 8, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - VHS - James Squires on “A Word on Words” WDCN Nashville for Read All About It!, May 21, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - VHS - CNN Prime News broadcast July 17, 1992, followed by James Squires on “Your Government” with Sue Wiley, April 1995 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - VHS - James Squires on “A Word on Words” WDCN Nashville for The Secrets of the Hopewell Box, March 20, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - VHS - Freedom Forum 75th Birthday Roast and Toast for Allen H. Neuharth, March 19, 1999 at Mayflower Hotel (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - VHS - Trinity Preparatory School Graduation Ceremony, June 1, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - VHS - Interview with Tom Leaher on Channel 27 for Horse of a Different Color, April 1, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - VHS - Florida Bankers Association Annual Meeting, August 2002 in Nassau, Bahamas (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - VHS - Appearance on “A Word on Words” Nashville Public Television for Horse of a Different Color, August 21, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - VHS - “Bookclub@KET” for Horse of a Different Color, May 6, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - VHS - Appearance on “Teddy Bart’s Round Table” for Horse of a Different Color, August 22 [2002-2003] (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Beta - Appearance on “Chicago Tonight” with John Callaway, WTTW-TV Chicago, January 9, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Beta - Appearance on Tom Snyder “Tomorrow” show, July 17, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Beta - CBS Morning News, April 12, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Beta - C-SPAN interview, unedited raw footage, March 19, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Beta - C-SPAN doping session, unedited raw footage, March 20, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Videocassettes - VHS format (Ross Perot presidential campaign - RESTRICTED)
      - VHS - Video message to Ross Perot from Mark Greene, March 24, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - VHS - “Peter Jennings Reporting: Who Is Ross Perot?”, June 29, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - VHS - Press conference with Tom Luce about Ed Rollins’ departure, July 15, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - VHS - Evening news about Ed Rollins’ resignation, July 15, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - VHS - News reports and James Squires, Hamilton Jordan appearance on the MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour, July 16, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - VHS - James Squires on “Your Government” with Sue Wiley, WLEX-TV Lexington, July 26, 1992 (recorded July 24, 1992) (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - VHS - James Squires on C-SPAN, viewer call-in show, August 3, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - VHS - Ross Perot on C-SPAN “A Conversation with Ross Perot” with Brian Lamb, August 19, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - VHS - James Squires on “Your Government” with Sue Wiley, WLEX-TV Lexington, October 18, 1992 (recorded October 16, 1992) (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - VHS - James Squires on MacNeil-Lehrer, Nightline and Today about Ross Perot and his daughter Carolyn’s wedding, October 28, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - VHS - James Squires on PBS, “The Perot Phenomenon,”, November 3, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Box 58
      - VHS -“Perot for President” campaign video [1992] (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - VHS - Coalition for a People’s Purse Amendment video [1992] (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - VHS - James Squires on Crossfire, “Perot, the Press and the Presidency” with Jack Nelson, February 12, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - VHS - James Squires on Crossfire, “Perot, the Press and the Presidency” with Jack Nelson, February 12, 1993 (copy 2) (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - VHS - James Squires on MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour about NAFTA, November 10, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - VHS - “How Ross Perot can Start a Dialogue with the News Media”, June 3, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - VHS - United We Stand America “Looking into the Mirror”, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - VHS - James Squires appearance on “Washington Journal”, March 21, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Audiocassettes and floppy diskettes
      - (Box 59)
      - Interview tape - Draper, W.Y. “Booty” (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Interview tape - Gillem, Zoe (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Interview tape - Gillem, Zoe (February 24); Robinson, Maude, (February 24, 1993) (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Interview tape - Norman, Jack, (February 16, 1994) (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Interview tape - Norman, Jack (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Interview tape - Robinson, Gale (March 1, 1994); Robinson, Judge Maude (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Interview tape - Robinson, Gale (March 2, 1994) (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Interview tape - Robinson, Gale, (March 3, 1994) (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Interview tape - Robinson, Maude, (February 24, 1993) (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Interview tape - Sheridan, Jake Jr.; Frank and Jane Anne [rest illegible] (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Cassette tape - Jim Loughman show, WGN radio, Sunday January 8, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Cassette tape - Jim Loughman show, WGN radio, Monday January 9, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Cassette tape - Interviews for Horse of a Different Color, side A; Part of panel discussion, “Do we need newspapers?” with James Squires, Malcolm Brown and Howard Kurtz on WDUQ at Duquesne University, Pittsburgh, PA, side B (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Audiobook - Horse of a Different Color audiocassettes, read by James Squires (8 cassettes) (Box 59, Folder 14)